<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on HyperBlog</title>
    <link>https://blog.hyperboly.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on HyperBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 20:08:56 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.hyperboly.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Memory Basics</title>
      <link>https://blog.hyperboly.net/posts/notes/memory-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 20:08:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hyperboly.net/posts/notes/memory-basics/</guid>
      <description>Memory is essential to understand for pwning in CTFs. Here, I will try to explain the structure of memory and behaviors for beginners in pwn.
Definition of Memory First, a basic definition of memory. Have you ever seen that long card in your computer with black squares on it? That&amp;rsquo;s memory. Most people (who watch Linus Tech Tips) know this as Random Access Memory (RAM), but at the core it is just temporary storage on your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Pwn</title>
      <link>https://blog.hyperboly.net/posts/notes/starting-pwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 19:05:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hyperboly.net/posts/notes/starting-pwn/</guid>
      <description>Pwn as a CTF category has always interested me because of the low level understanding it requires to be good at it. Turns out I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at it, so here are my notes to try and organize what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned. The pico primer really helped me with this. CryptoCat&amp;rsquo;s tutorial is also great for learning.
Definitions: Abstraction I find that many people trying to get into computers get confused with abstraction as I did before, so I&amp;rsquo;ll try to explain it in simple terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPU passthrough for RX6600XT</title>
      <link>https://blog.hyperboly.net/posts/guides/gpupassthroughamd6600/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 18:09:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hyperboly.net/posts/guides/gpupassthroughamd6600/</guid>
      <description>A Comprehensive Guide on GPU Passthroughs in Proxmox Some Prerequisites and Notes This method of passing through my GPU works for:
 Kernel: 5.15.30 Proxmox Version 7.2 TUF Gaming X570 Plus Motherboard Dual Radeon RX6600XT Asus GPU Ryzen 7 5800X CPU  In the BIOs for your host computer (where Proxmox is installed) settings, these options should be modified:
 Secure boot: Off CPU Settings:  SUM: On PSS: On   PCI Subsystem Settings:  Above 4G Encoding: On SR-IOV Support: On   AMD CBS:  IOMMU: On    The Passthrough Process This is the part of the process where everything is either done in an ssh session, on the host computer&amp;rsquo;s shell, or the webGUI for proxmox.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
